

# **PROFILE**

I am a communicative and studious 27 year old woman with a calm and caring personality.

By using my analytics skills I strive to provide clear and accurate information while running the extra mile to understand the content that I am working on.

Outside of work I like music, travelling, nature and reading. I also have a basic understanding of multiple languages and rudimentary education in web design and IT.

#### **CONTACT**

PHONE:

+31 62 202 29 17

EMAIL:

pulaylilla@gmail.com

# **INTERESTS**

Languages IT Music

Nature

# **LANGUAGES**

Hungarian (Native)
English (Professional working proficiency)
German (Elementary proficiency)
Norwegian (Elementary proficiency)
Dutch (Elementary proficiency)

# LILLA PULAY

Name: Lilla Pulay, dr.

Place of Residence: Lelystad, Netherlands Date of Birth: 18th November 1991

Gender: Female
Nationality: Hungarian
Driver license: Full Car

## **EDUCATION**

Károli Gáspár University - Faculty of Law

2011 - 2017

Jurist (MA)

Qualification of diploma: Cum Laude

Károli Gáspár University - Faculty of Law

2013 - 2016

**International Relations Expert (BA)** 

Specialisation: International Economic Relations

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Booking.com

### **Customer Service Guest Specialist**

May 2019 - November 2019

Assisting customers with their requests by handling phone calls, emails and messages and using various online tools as part of a multilingual team in a fast-paced environment.

#### **Deloitte Hungary**

### Tax Consultant, Global Innovation and Investment Incentives (Gi3)

September 2018 - March 2019

Analysing subsidy opportunities and R&D activities of companies, preparing and translating client presentations, supporting business development and scoping potential new clients, research and office administration.

### Budapest Metropolitan Police (BRFK) Administrator, AETR

October 2017 - September 2018

Administrative tasks, contacting clients, drafting decision proposals and keeping track of the changes in relevant legal regulation.

#### Dr. Zsombor Ercsey, Attorney at Law Intern

Intern

March 2016

Legal research regarding various tax systems, international taxation, administrative tasks, office routine, drafting and translating emails for clients.

# IV and XV District Court of Budapest

August 2015 - September 2015

Getting acquainted with court administration, legal research, participating in court hearings and drafting verdicts.

#### Dr. András Somos, Attorney at Law Intern

March 2015 - April 2015

Contacting clients, administrative tasks, office routine and drafting documents for clients and administrative bodies.